This is a screenshot of our meta ads manager from the last 26 hours.
We booked five qualified leads at just 20 dirhams per lead who will get on a sales
call with our agency to explore our full scale offer and see how we can help them
grow their business in 2025.
Now, even if we close one of these five
qualified leads, our customer acquisition costs for our full scale offer will only
be 100 dirhams of ad spend, which is a tiny fraction of the price of our packages.
Now, I have to be honest with you, it wasn't always this simple for us.
It was only months ago where my partner and I were spending thousands of
dollars every single month on figuring out a system that would bring us clients.
Who one needed exactly what we had to sell to have the budget to pay for our
services and three were ready to get started with our agency ASAP and after
Over years of trial and error, we finally came across a system that started working
for us consistently and growing our business month after month.
And that's where everything clicked.
We started growing, expanding the team, and we even moved out to an office in the heart
of Dubai, which is exactly where I'm recording this video from right now.
So what suddenly changed?
How do we go from a couple of broke, burnt out guys in their twenties to operating an
agency that has helped 50 plus businesses consistently grow month after month?
We'll explain it all in this very short video.
My name is Mohan, and what I'm about to share with you could completely transform how your business can grow in 2025.
Now, before I move into exactly how the system works, I want to first focus on you and your business specifically.
If you're watching this video, it's probably because of one of three reasons.
One, you've trusted other freelancers or agencies with your business's marketing, but you've been burned so far with really bad results.
Two, you've tried running ads, posting on social media, and taking on all of the marketing tasks yourself, but haven't seen any real changes so far.
Three, you've never had a proper marketing system
for your business and you're looking to grow ASAP.
What all of these three categories have in common
is that they're currently starving their business of cash
because they don't have a reliable
customer acquisition strategy
that can feed their business month after month.
What makes XMA different is that we've developed
a complete digital marketing ecosystem
that combines content production, advertising,
CRM solutions, and AI automations into one cohesive system,
which we call the Link Flow system.
And the lead flow system is a full solution where every component of your marketing machine
works together to generate leads, nourish prospects, and help convert them into paying
customers.
And we've been able to implement this exact system for over 50 clients so far.
Take this luxury bag brand, for example.
We took them from a couple thousand dirhams all the way up to 400,000 dirhams in generated
revenue, and we increased their customer retention rate to 12.65%, which is in the top 1% of
the industry for a luxury brand.
We also work with the UAE commerce phenomenon, The Flower Guys, who took Dubai by storm in 2025.
We built their website, optimized their landing page, ran their ad campaigns, and even created content for their business,
a bunch of which were in collaboration with Noon.com.
Or take Formatic Car Infos, who have been using our lead flow system for months.
Aside from generating them qualified leads every single day,
we also created a brand new, optimized landing page for them, which has significantly increased their conversion rates.
Or take a look at PacMat, one of the UAE's leading e-commerce software companies.
They have been a client of ours for over three years and use our exact
workflow system to generate qualified prospects for their business month after month.
So you don't need a seven figure marketing department to grow your business exponentially in 2025.
All you need is the right system.
And if you start now, if you implement the right system into your business today,
the gap between you and your competitors will go exponentially every single week.
Because while they're out there testing different marketing trends,
jumping between agencies or hiring cheap freelancers,
you're just doing what's working,
driving the gap between you and your competitors even further.
Now aside from some of the client wins I shared with you earlier,
so far we've been able to manage over 3 million dirhams in ad spend.
generate over 30,000 qualified leads,
and have produced over 300 video ads that have converted browsers into buyers.
So what makes our system work?
Well, the game of advertising is actually very straightforward.
One, you pay money to get your message in front of strangers.
Two, a percent of those strangers will become leads.
Three, a percent of those leads will become customers.
And four, at the end of it all, the money you made should have exceeded what you spent.
So in principle, success is when you put a dollar in and get two plus dollars back for your business.
In order for you to win at this game, you need to make sure that your system is acting like a machine
that is constantly pushing strangers to become customers every single day.
And this is where our complete process comes into play.
The first step of our complete lead flow solution is to create high quality ads for your business.
And we do this from A to Z for all of our clients,
meaning one, we'll analyze your business
and research your industry.
Two, have our copywriters craft persuasive scripts
that address your prospects' pain points,
present a solution, and hook your audience in
from start to finish.
Then our team of professional videographers
will come to your business with a model of your choosing
and shoot all of your ads in one day.
And lastly, our team of editors will then take that raw footage and
transform it into conversion focused ads that are meant to drive action.
Once content creation is done, the second step is an integrating our
custom CRM solution, which is the backbone of your lead management process.
The CRM system will instantly capture your leads from meta ad platforms,
respond to new leads that have come through the door immediately, and
have a custom AI chatbot engage with your prospect and push them
further down your pipeline.
On average, prospects who receive an immediate follow-up
are seven times more likely to book a sales call
and five times more likely to become customers.
The best part is we set it all up for you.
The custom fields, automated workflows,
WhatsApp templates, and AI chatbot instructions
Everything will be configured specifically for your business.
Once the CRM is set up, the third step is launching your ads.
This is where we put your ads in front of your ideal customer profile to generate you quality leads consistently,
which ends up feeding the CRM and pushing prospects further down your pipeline.
And the fourth and final component is your campaign management,
where we monitor and optimize your ad campaigns to make sure your pipeline is always filled with quality leads
and your CRM and AI automations are fully sustained.
So now that you know exactly what you need to do
to take your marketing to the next level in 2025,
you're faced with three options.
You can continue what you're doing,
move down the same path and hope for different results.
You can try and replicate the system yourself,
which can take months and thousands of dollars to pull off,
or you can partner with us and implement the Leadflow system
into your business in a matter of weeks.
Now, I understand this is an important decision
for you to make.
This is why we look forward to having you on a call with us
so we can discuss in detail exactly how we can help
your business grow in 2025.
Thanks for watching this video.
I hope it's been informative
and I look forward to seeing you on our call.